Kyle Peacock

815 Spring Drive | Walnut Creek, CA 93498 | 925.978.3489 | kylpeacock@gmail.com

Objective

To create value for my employer by crafting excellent user experiences and positive impressions of the company. I want to find an agile team where my passion for intuitive design and scalable solutions will contribute to my project's success.

Education

August 2015 - December 2015

J.D. Candidate

U.C. Davis School of Law, California

August 2011 - May 2015

Bachelor of the Arts in Political Science & Philosophy

Wheaton College, Illinois

Experience

January 2016 - Current

Programmer | Galvanize Full Stack | San Francisco

Recieved professional training in the latest Javascriptbased full stack web development.

January 2015 - May 2015

Policy Intern | Cabrini Green Legal Aid | Chicago

Produced publications for the HB 484 Education bill in Illinois for the Spring Legislative Session, providing administrative support, graphic design, and raising awareness.

May 2014 - August 2014

City Manager Intern | City of Walnut Creek

Responsibilities included research, writing, graphic design, photography and proofreading.

June 2011 - August 2014

Lifeguard | Clarke Memorial Swim Center | Walnut Creek

Seasonal lifeguard and swim instructor employed by the City of Walnut Creek.

Recognitions

April 2016

2nd place of 30+ teams | AngelHack SF

Desgined, produced, and pitched a grocery management application in 24 hours with a team of five.

August 2014

Had a three page article on the history of Walnut Creek published in the city's newsletter, the Nutshell.

Skills

•

Javascript

- NodeJS
- React
- Express
- Git

- Public Speaking
- Agile Development
- User Experience
- Product

Management

Creative Cloud

Personal

Former competitive swimmer, debate coach, classically trained singer. Getting married this summer!